Finding Aid for Institute of Science and Technology (University of Michigan) records, 1950-1989.
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Proposal File
  Proposal Files, 1959-1987 (0 7 linear feet) are arranged by proposal number. The files typically containing appoint forms for individuals funded by IST, also requests for other types of IST support (equipment, travel, etc.); occasionally included are final copies of research completed with IST assistance. The series also includes a card index (arranged by name) to the files and a notebook index (arranged by proposal number) to the proposals themselves.
  - Card index to files (Box 25)
    (2 card files arranged alphabetically)
  - Notebook index to proposals (Box 25)
    (arranged by proposal number)
  - Numbered files (Box 26)
    - 1-155 (Box 26)
    - 156-391 (Box 27)
    - 392-520 (Box 28)
    - 521-629 (Box 29)
    - 630-3092 (Box 30)
    - 4048-4555 (Box 31)
    - Special projects, 4 folders (Box 31)
- Audio-Visual Material
  The Audio-Visual materials series consists of photographs and videotapes. Photographs series, includes images ca. 1960s, of Willow Run Laboratories and of the IST building on the University's North Campus; photos of 1964 open house exhibition upon occasion of the opening of the IST building; photos, 1984-1985, taken of the events occasioned by the 25th anniversary of IST; unarranged slides of IST programs and activities; and videocassette of TV public service spots on the subject of technology.
  - Photos (Box 32)
  - Videotapes (Box 32)